Anurag Peddi Student

\$919095544 □ anuragpeddi71@gmail.com **30/12/1998** AnuragAnalog

★ anuraganalog.github.io in Anurag Peddi

5-11-50/3A2, Anuraganilayam, Priyadarshini Nagar, Nirmal, 504106 Nirmal, India

PROFILE

An undergraduate with a passion for machine learning and data science, I have experience understanding and analysing data in order to drive growth. Provide the necessary insights, analytics, and visualisation to aid decisionmaking for a fashion forecasting company.

LANGUAGES

C, Python, ReactJS, SQL, R, MongoDB, HTML, C++, Java, CSS, Git, Android, AWS, Data Analytics, Excel

SKILLS

Telugu, Hindi, English

EDUCATION

Integrated M.Tech 2017 - present University of Hyderabad ☑ Hyderabad, India

With an aggregate of 9.32

Intermediate(M.P.C) 2015 - 2017Narayana Junior College Hyderabad, India

With an aggregate of 98.3%

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Data Science Intern 05/2021 - present

Stylumia 🗗

• Made an Intuitive Covid19 Prediction model for India's third wave

- Building Custom ETL pipelines, Optimization of Inventory Allocation and Pipelines for hyperparameter tuning of ML models on real-time data
- Build some time-series models using modern frameworks
- Converted data into actionable insights by predicting and modelling future outcomes

Machine Learning Intern

10/2020 - 12/2020Hyderabad, India Grroom ♂

- As an Intern, My tasks were Image Scraping, Model building, Model tuning for object detection(yolo) in Fashion Domain, to yield good mAP and accuracy.
- During my internship, I also researched cost-effective ways of deploying multiple models on the web and suggested them.

Summer School 05/2019 - 06/2019 Chennai Mathematical Institute 🛮 Chennai, India

• Using Random forests and SVM, I created a machine learning model to predict whether the price will rise or fall.

• Learned about the financial statistics, Markov chains, portfolio optimization etc.

Anurag Peddi 1/2

PROJECTS

Try Every Machine Learning Algorithm 🛮

06/2020 - present

A Playground where you may experiment with various machine learning algorithms on a given dataset by tinkering with its hyper-parameters until you get bored.

Pen Ink Differentiation using CNN

11/2020 - 04/2021

Currently, I'm working on a research project with my professor on detecting pen forgery detection using CNNs

Twitter Data Sentiment Analysis

05/2020 - 06/2020

COVID19 Twitter Data Analysis, Indian Sentiment Analysis Using Tweets after Three Lockdowns

Online Video Streaming

10/2019 - 11/2019

Using HTML, PHP, JS, and CSS, I created an online video streaming website where the admin may add videos to be seen by users.

Many more projects which includes ML and DL Concepts

Android, web, and IoT integration (for example object detection, gender and age prediction etc.)

COURSES

Tableau Fundamentals 🛮 03/2021 - 04/2021

DataCamp

TensorFlow Developer Professional Certificate 04/2020 - 06/2020

deeplearning.ai

Deep Learning Specialization 03/2020 - 05/2020

deeplearning.ai



E CERTIFICATES

IEEEXtreme 13.0 ☑

HackNITP 3.0 □

Smart India Hackathon

Amazon Machine Learning Challenge

- Participated in a 24 hour Online Hackathon - Secured a global rank of 295 and an all-India rank of 29.
- Built an audio sentiment predictor.
- Secured 5th Place in the Al Domain

- Shortlisted for Smart India Hackathon - Automated Land use

classification based on Multi-spectral Imagery using the DL model

- Created a MultiClass classification model for a large corpus, which gives comparable accuracy to state of art models.

ORGANISATIONS

Neural Network Visualizer 🛮

08/2020 - present

A module which creates a neural network image with the given architecture.

IEEE Hyderabad Section

06/2019 - 12/2019

Volunteer

I also competed in the IEEEXtreme 13.0 24-hour coding competition during my volunteer time.

Hyderabad, India

2/2 Anurag Peddi